Get in, Lucifer. We're going shopping.
>> [music]
[music]
>> But, let's get into the tea. I don't
even really know where to start. As some
of you may know, actually none of y'all
know because I keep my life private as
um I am
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hold [music] me tight.
Let me go.
In my heart
and in my soul.
Hold me tight.
>> [music]
>> Let me go.
In my heart
and in my soul.
Hold me tight.
>> [music]
>> Let me go.
In my heart
and in my soul.
Hold me tight.
Let me go.
In my heart [music]
and in my
Hold me tight.
Let me go.
In my heart
and in my
>> [music]
>> Hold me tight.
Let me go.
In my heart
>> [music]
>> and in my
Hold me tight.
Let me go.
>> [music]
>> In my heart
and in my
Hold me tight.
Let me go.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hello girls. Welcome back to the
channel.
You guys
You guys, I'm in a great mood. I'm in a
great mood today.
It's one of those days. It's one of
those days. You want to know why?
It's honestly it's a bunch of reasons,
but
um hello, we just hit 90k subscribers.
LIKE OH MY GOD, not y'all really really
[\h__\h] with me. Like I
I am just
I am honestly shocked at how quickly
we've gotten here because it feels like
I was just celebrating like 20k. Y'all
remember that? Like it was only a few
videos ago whenever we were celebrating
20k, 40k, 50k, and now we're almost at
100k.
You guys, my goal for the end of the
year was to hit 100k subscribers, but I
feel like we're going to do it before
that, probably by my birthday. My
birthday is September 22nd. So, that's
my goal.
10 more K before my birthday.
Honestly, we might be able to do it
before then if I really stay on the ball
for real. But, yeah, that's the goal by
September What's today?
It is Thursday, July 9th today, okay?
So,
we could possibly do it, and I'm just so
excited because 100k,
I'm doing my big giveaway, and I kind of
want to ask y'all, what do y'all want?
What do y'all want from me? Because this
is big. So, I I might I might splurge on
y'all a little bit. I might, so let me
know what y'all want in the comments.
Like don't put nothing crazy. Like I'm
not going to buy y'all no new car, okay?
Chill. But, what y'all want? Something
Something you've been eyeing or
something that you feel like you maybe
don't want to spend your own money on or
something like that or something girly,
something cute, something that I have.
It's going to be I don't know. I don't
know if I want to do like a big thing or
like a big thing and some little things
with some medium things. I don't know.
You guys just let me know. But, yeah,
I'm just I'm in a great mood. I'm really
excited. I have this cute little outfit
on. Like,
it's just I feel like it's just goes
with the vibe today because I didn't
even tell y'all what we're doing today.
We're going shopping. [snorts]
So, like, it's just it's a great day to
be me. It's a great day to be Journey
Carter and it's a great day to be
watching my channel because you guys are
coming along with me, duh. And I'm not
even going to lie to y'all.
>> [clears throat]
>> Something in my throat, okay.
Ooh, I have not been feeling the best.
I've kind of been in a little rut.
Now, well, I don't know if rut is really
the right word, but I've just been
feeling so many different type of
things. This Mercury retrograde, number
one. Number two, it's some personal
stuff that I got going on in my life,
which I feel like I am going to share
with y'all today. Whenever we get in the
car, I need to get a coffee and stuff,
okay? We need to get out the door cuz
I'm a little I was supposed to be out
the door an hour ago. I had to finish
filming this freaking campaign for
Victoria's Secret. Oh my god.
>> [gasps]
>> And I just did a campaign with
Victoria's Secret. Like, I'm just it's
it's it's a great week to be me. It
really is. Um
But, anyways, sorry.
Sorry. I should have been out the door a
while ago, but
but that's besides the point. I need to
come on, say what's up to the girly
pops. But, when we get in the car, I'm
going to go get a coffee,
uh maybe a little snack or something
before we go shop. And I'm going to
share with you guys what's been going on
in my life because I know you guys have
questions. A bunch of y'all have been
asking me
annoyingly. But, it's okay cuz I love
y'all. And I just need to share it cuz I
want to be real. I want to be honest. I
want to be raw. Um I've just been going
through some life changes, okay? And
we'll talk about that later today. But
um in today's video, I want to go to
Zara because I've been feeling skirts
lately and I've been seeing on Zara they
have these cute like summer skirts and
like matching sets and everything. So,
I'm just going to go into Zara and have
Zara tell me what I need to try on. And
we're just going to like go try some
clothes, go shopping a little bit. I
want to hit Lush. I need to get a new
phone case. I'm just going to go
shopping today and you guys are coming
along. So, I don't know what stores
we'll end up at, but just know we're
doing that. And then I have a girls
night later tonight. I'm so excited like
a girls night planned like oh my god.
It's just it's today is great. Today is
seriously great like
if you guys are feeling down,
I'm pushing all of my positive, loud,
bright energy to y'all today, okay?
Get up.
If you're laying down, get up. All
right? Get up. Go shop. Go do something
for yourself, okay? It's Sunday, right?
Sunday. Praise the Lord.
And also praise yourself, okay? Yes.
This is your little nudge, your little
reminder to get up and do something for
you today, okay? Cuz that's what I'm
doing. So, yeah, after we go shopping,
I'mma come home and get ready to go see
the girls. We are going to the Monarch
in Dallas. If you've ever been,
if you know, you know. It's so cute.
It's like a rooftop bar and the whole
like side of the restaurant is windows.
And so, it's like you're eating over the
entire city of Dallas. They have a nice
pretty bar. And it's just bougie and
classy and cute. So, me and my girls are
going to go. I haven't seen them in a
while, so we're going to catch up with
them. Um I'm going to try to film as
much as I can of that, too. But yeah,
any other updates that I need to let you
guys know about? Hmm, let me check my
little
checklist. You guys know me, very type A
Virgo code, okay? Mhm mhm. Okay, I think
we're good. I think I've covered
everything. Wait.
How are we doing?
How are you guys doing?
What's been going on with y'all?
Cuz y'all know me, I'll just talk about
myself the whole time, but what's going
on with y'all?
Are y'all good?
It's mid-July.
Hot summer [singing] nights.
Mid-July,
when you and I
forever are.
How are y'all doing? It is mid-July.
What's been going on with y'all summer?
Are y'all working? Are y'all outside?
Are y'all traveling? Are y'all
babysitting? Are y'all at the pool?
What's up? What's been going on with
y'all? Let me know in the comments.
But, you guys know me, I will yap and
yap and yap. So, without further ado,
get in loser, we're going shopping.
>> [music]
>> Hi, how are you?
>> How about you?
>> Good. Can I do your golden eagle?
>> Got your iced tea.
>> I yes.
>> No problem. What size?
>> Let's do
Can I see your small cup?
>> Yep, for sure.
>> I don't want it too Yeah, that's
perfect. Yes.
Oh, it's good. I'm in a great mood
actually. How are you?
>> I'm good.
>> Good?
>> It's pretty hot though, obviously.
>> It's so hot. Oh my god.
>> Texas heat gets like 100.
>> Literally.
>> Any big plans today?
>> I'm just going shopping.
>> Ooh.
>> Very girly today, yeah. Yeah.
>> Like I'll go shopping and I'm just like,
I want this sometimes and most of the
time it's like, there's little parts of
it I don't like.
>> Yeah.
>> And when thrifting it's like, sometimes
you can cut something and
>> Yes. You get a tip today.
>> Here's your iced tea.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Of course. And did I get your straw?
>> Thank you so much. Oh, thank you.
>> Of course.
>> Thank you.
>> Of course. Have a nice day.
>> You too.
Oop. Oh Oh god, you guys fell. Oh my
god, I hope you guys are okay down
there. Coffee's secured. Period.
I always get the Golden Eagle at Dutch
Bros.
And [music] you guys, they're so
freaking friendly. Like, I love Every
time I go through the drive-thru at a
Dutch Bros, they're so freaking nice.
Like, their customer service is
top-tier.
Uh,
the sound.
Taste test.
Mhm.
Beautiful.
Beautiful. You guys, it's so freaking
hot and I had to turn down the AC so you
guys could hear me for real. I'm going
to turn it up just a little notch
because
Is that too much? Wait.
How's that?
Ooh,
I don't want it to be too much. I want
you guys to be able to hear me for real.
But, let's get into the tea. Why we are
here. Okay.
Let's get into the tea. I don't even
really know where to start. Okay.
I don't really know where to start, but
um
as
many of you guys As some of you may
know, actually none of y'all know
because I keep my life private as well.
Um I am single.
Yes, I'm single now, you guys. I've been
single for about
3 months now. Um
like officially like
2 months, 2 and 1/2 or something,
whatever.
Whatever. I'm not super technical on it.
It feels like
a long time. So, it's been up around 3
months. And it's been difficult for me.
Um just because like
I am a relationship type of girl. So,
like I be lonely because I don't really
have rosters. Like, I don't have hella
men that I'm talking to at all times.
Like, I just
I don't do that. Number one, because men
are boring, okay? Men are not as cool as
me and my homegirls. So,
I'm not just hanging out with [\h__\h]
Like, I
No. And then number two, I need to heal,
right?
And then number three, it's just
dating today is crazy. Like, I haven't
been in the field in a while. And how
are y'all doing this? Like, genuinely.
Genuinely, how are y'all doing this?
Because dating right now
is so weird. Like, I haven't even been
on a date. Now, don't get me wrong.
I've hung out with men, but I ain't
really been on a date for real.
I
I'm getting sweaty. I'm getting hot
because I don't like this topic and I
don't like and I don't even like the
fact that I'm really sharing this job
because I feel like I just hate being
vulnerable. I really do. Um but
this has been a challenging season for
me. Like, seriously. I don't know
what to do. Like,
it's it's I want to say it's honestly
pretty hard for me [clears throat]
because
my ex was like
he was like my best friend. Like, he was
like my bestie boo. Like, we just did
basically everything together. And like,
sometimes I'll be finding myself like
something something funny will happen or
like something that only he would
understand and I just want to like pick
up the phone and call him.
But then I'm like,
so I don't do it. You know what I mean?
Like, it's just things about moving on
that's like weird. It's just hard and
like
gross. And then it's like
and then another thing too, this is kind
of toxic of me, but I feel like
everybody kind of does this too whenever
they're like single or moving on. It's
so so hard to not compare the new person
that you're talking to to your ex. Like,
you're like, oh, like, my ex would have
never did that." Or, "Oh, you're so much
better at this than my ex." Or like,
just comparing them so much. I need to
stop doing that. Like,
it's it's hindering. It's hindering me.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know. Like, it's just weird.
Like, I don't know. And like, it's no
bad blood, I want to say, on my end. I
don't know.
I don't know.
It's a lot of emotions. It's a lot of
emotions. [clears throat] We're probably
both pissed at each other, mad at each
other.
You know, all of the things. But, it's
fine.
I'm good. I just want to let y'all know
I'm good, but I do want to be real and
raw with y'all and let y'all know like,
I be going through it, too, okay? I'm
not always
happy like, no, no, no, no. Moving out
like, I be I be going through it. I be
going through it. And I'm just also
having days where it's like, what am I
supposed to do? Like, what? Just like,
what am I supposed to do? Like, yes, I
have my career and everything. Like,
that's never stopping. Like, I never put
that on hold for a minute. I'm always
uploading, always doing my stuff. But,
it's like,
what do I do now? Like, I can just do
anything and talk to anyone? Like, it's
just weird. It's so weird. It's almost
like too much freedom. And so, I don't
know
like what to do with myself, you know
what I mean?
In that aspect. Um, I have definitely
been hanging out with my girls a lot
more. Um,
hanging out with my friends a lot more.
I've honestly been hanging out with my
family, too, more, which is good.
Not that my ex took me away from any of
those things, but it's just giving me
like more time to like really just like
tend to my other relationships, I guess,
and, you know, water them a little bit
more.
Um,
but, it's just weird. Like, it's so
weird being single. Now, I will say I do
love the freedom of, you know, not
having to put someone else's feelings
before yours, not having to constantly
like check in with somebody. Like, just
the freedom of that. And it really only
hits me that I'm single at night. At
night, at night, at night. At night
boy, I'll be ready to
unblock. No.
>> [laughter]
>> No, I shouldn't, but like
I No, like I just y'all, night time is
really what I be I'll be like
I'll be having to call my friends like,
"Hey, talk to me. Like, keep me from
doing something that I really really
should not be doing right now. You feel
me?" And then also like pumping my own
gas and putting my earrings in and tying
the back of my clothes and my dresses
and [\h__\h] Like, I don't have no one to
do that for me no more.
And it's just a little bit I'm a little
bit more independent.
Um
because yeah, my ex did a lot for me.
Which I now realize that
being on my own now, it's like, "Damn, I
don't have anybody to freaking tie my
dress up." But anyways, but anyways,
it's just like little stuff like that
that you kind of like got to adjust to
and stuff like that. Um and then
and then also
very real
>> [laughter]
>> I
have not
you know
in so long. I feel like I'M GOING CRAZY.
AHH!
I'M GOING CRAZY. I'm clearly going
crazy.
It's clear. Like, I'm going crazy. Like,
I'm just like, "Oh my god, how do people
be celebrate?"
How genuinely? That's that's the
question. Like, how are y'all doing this
for years, months on end?
Who we?
It's crazy. I just feel like I saw this
tweet the other day
and it said, "My poor coochie probably
thinks I died."
>> [gasps]
>> Sorry.
Sorry, y'all. I'll be I just be cracking
myself up. Um and also I laugh too
whenever I'm being like vulnerable or
like when I'm nervous or just like
you know, but
yeah.
That That's a little life update, and
it's just been causing me to be kind of
in like this little I wouldn't even say
rut. It's not a rut. It's just changing
It's just my life is changing. It's just
like a big life change, and um
I'm a lover girl, so it's just hard for
me to like adjust to not having someone
to freaking fall asleep on the phone
with every night. You feel me? But But
it's cool, and I'm good. I promise y'all
I'm good. I'm I'm promise y'all I am
okay. But um I just wanted to share that
with y'all and be honest with my girly
pops. And also so you guys can stop
asking me, okay? And um yeah, that's
That's where we are. That's where I am,
navigating this. Are you guys Are you
guys good? Are you guys single? Are you
guys going through the same thing? I
don't know.
Let me know. We can talk about it in the
comments. Honestly, I don't know if I
want to talk about this in the comments,
to be honest. Y'all just let me know the
giveaway and how y'all's summer's been,
okay? I don't know if I want to talk
about relationships, but we can. We can
talk about yours, but we're not going to
talk about mine. Um this is as much as
I'm going to share cuz y'all know I
don't be sharing my personal personal
super personal like stuff on here. Y'all
know what y'all know, basically. You
know what I mean? Y'all know what I tell
you at the end of the day. But I figured
I would just kind of let y'all know
because I want to remain authentic on
this channel, and I want you guys to
connect with me on that level, like
number one relatability. I don't want
y'all to think that I'm just um like
Like Like I want y'all to be able to
relate to me on some levels. You know
what I mean? Like I I I want to be
y'all's big sister for real. Like I want
to help y'all through life, and I know a
lot of y'all are inspired by me, so I
just want to be authentic and raw and
real. So
that's why I'm doing that, but
just know it's really hard and icky for
me to do this, okay?
But
anyways, I'm about to suffocate in this
car because I turned off my AC to talk
to y'all.
So, I'm going to turn it back up.
Oh.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
But, anyways, um that's enough of that.
Now, we're about to go shopping. Okay,
so I'll see y'all when we get to the
mall.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay. Hey, girls. I'm doing a little
voice over because there was music in
the dressing rooms. But, anyways,
starting off strong, I got this blue
bandage dress, which I'm not going to
lie,
>> [music]
>> I don't think I liked it. It didn't
really like fit my body how I wanted it.
It was cute. The color was really
gorgeous, but it was so loose and it
didn't really [music] like hug me how I
wanted to. I don't know. I It just It
just didn't fit the best. [music] And
then, I got this most gorgeous tank top.
It's white. It's lace. I ended up taking
both of these items home. These shorts,
get into it, okay? These are perfect for
summer. I love the [music] pink. This
outfit is actually an outfit that I
would wear together. I would wear these
shoes, these shorts, this shirt all
together. I think it's so summery and
cute. Like, these are my favorite
[music] two items that I tried on like
out of this whole lineup, okay? Then, I
got these shorts, which they were a
little too short. Um I don't know. I
just love the color. As you can see, I
picked like a bunch of items that were
very vibrant. I'm feeling summery vibes,
[music] but I didn't end up getting
these. And then I found this same shirt,
but in pink. Gorgeous. I picked that up,
too. And then I found this skirt, which
I kind of like the vibe. It's giving me
like fairy girl princess la la la, like
super girly, super feminine.
>> [music]
>> I really, really like this. I didn't end
up getting the skirt. I kind of want to
go back and shop again because there was
just so many goodies inside this store.
And then, look at this top. Is this not
the most perfect
>> [music]
>> top ever? I definitely got this, put it
in my cart. It's hanging up in my closet
as we speak. I'm obsessed. [music] And
then I tried on this like crop top
shirt. It was a little bit too cropped
for me. Um I didn't end up getting it,
and I just tried it on with those other
shorts that I did not end up getting,
either.
Ooh, and then I found like this
bubblegum blue and pink [music]
two-piece set, which I thought was so
freaking cute. Like I'm just loving all
of the colors that Adika has. Like I
didn't even know that Adika was in
store. But I just found so many good
pieces, and I really just had to share
with y'all. Like look at this freaking
yellow shirt. [music]
This is so 2000s coded. I love it. I
really, really loved everything that I
tried on. And then I tried this little
tank, too. She was cute, but I didn't
end up getting her. But trust, I will be
back at this store, this location. Their
customer service was amazing. I loved
it. But here I'm checking out, and we're
about to head to Zara.
>> [music]
[music]
>> And we're back for our second try-on
haul. You guys, this skirt is purple my
color?
>> [music]
>> Like, oh my god, I am obsessed. I love
love love this. The only reason I did
not get it was because it was so big. It
was too big on me, but I just had to try
it on. And then I also wish I got this
skirt. How cute is this freaking skirt?
I didn't end up getting it because why
was it $78? Okay, Zara, chill. [music]
Not too much. Not too much. But then I
tried on these and I absolutely loved. I
ended up taking these home with me.
Perfect for running errands, very flowy,
airy,
>> [music]
>> perfect for me, exactly what I was
looking for. Copped. And then I found
these. I thought these were cute. I
didn't get them because I feel like you
could buy these at Target, but they were
really cute. I loved the color. I loved
the fit, but they were like $50.
>> [music]
>> And Zara, no, ma'am. So, I didn't get
them. Um and then I tried on the most
gorgeous [music] lavender silk dress.
You guys, this was so freaking gorgeous.
I wish I got it. I wish I would have got
it. It was like $145.
But oh my god, I was obsessed with this.
I felt like Princess Jasmine. [music]
And then I ended up getting this little
polka dot top. I thought she was super
cute.
>> Okay.
>> Y'all, we trying to figure out how to do
this.
>> I'm cooking it.
>> Where do I scan it?
Wait, is this where I scan it? Right
here?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Sorry, we we
We all learning over here.
>> Yeah.
>> Where?
>> So, I guess we're going to watch her do
it.
>> Okay.
>> Look at that paper.
>> The whole thing? Like is it all in?
>> Oh.
Oh.
Okay.
>> So, you don't have to
scan it one by one?
>> No, we're literally lost.
>> I scan it one by one. I think I know how
to do this.
Okay, so we put it in here.
Put our telephone.
Wait, so is it doing it by itself?
That's high-tech.
>> Okay, this is confusing.
>> Oh my god.
Y'all, it literally pops up right here
on the screen.
Okay.
>> [gasps]
>> This is so crazy.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my god, technology is crazy.
Have I been living under a rock, or have
you always been able to check out by
yourself at Zara?
This is crazy.
Like, wow.
Yes.
That was the most easiest, seamless
checkout.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. So cool.
So easy.
Wow.
Bags secured. I love it here.
>> [music]
>> Now, it's time to go to Lush, my
favorite. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Ooh,
you guys, I am back in the car. I feel
like I've been shopping for hours and
hours on end, [clears throat]
but
bags secured, we did great. I also went
into Alo, but it was so hectic in there.
I literally could not even film in it. I
was getting overstimulated in there. We
went into Lush. I didn't end up getting
anything in Lush because I kind of
wanted to look at their massage bars
that I was telling you about, and I
didn't like really any of the flavors.
So, yeah. But, you guys know I love
their Super Milk, and then I have their
little like
travel-sized rub-on blush balm perfume
thingies. I don't know. I love them. I
love Lush. And every time I'm in the
mall, I just go into Lush. It smells so
good in there. Also, too, I wanted to
show you guys this magical little thing.
I think I've talked about it on my
channel before. I got this one from
Rizos Curls, but you see how like my
hair is coming up? It's like a wax
stick. You guys probably have heard of
these before, but
it comes so in handy. Like, you just
brush it back, and look.
Boom.
Perfect. See how like all the hair is
like you can't even really tell. All the
hair is coming up, but all you have to
do is just boom.
It's perfect for like my slicked-back
days.
Whenever you want your hair to just
stay.
When you want your hair to just stay.
Mhm. It's a little tip for the girlies.
I keep this in like all my purses,
literally. I have like four of these.
This one's from Rizos Curls. You can get
them on Amazon. You can get them
anywhere, literally. And then I feel
like my freaking lips need some TLC.
Today, I'm using my Moroccan Oil.
This is the Moroccan Mint Tea Lip Balm
from Moroccan Oil, and I love this
stuff. It's so moisturizing on my lips.
Like, look at that. So good. I'm about
to grab a snack on the way home. Just
something small because I have grilled
dinner in like 3 hours. So, I'm about to
head home, get ready for that, pick out
an outfit. I might have you guys pick
out an outfit with me. I don't know yet.
Just depends on if I'm rushing or not.
But yeah, I just want to check in. I'm
about to head home and I will see you
guys when I'm all dolled up. Well, I'm
kind of dolled up right now, but I'll
see you guys when I'm all dolled up for
girls night, okay?
Love you.
Hello. Okay, I'm back and I'm ready and
I'm dressed. But I just have to a couple
more touches. I have my Chanel-ica
jewelry
to go down the middle and then this is
the dress.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> So cute. Oh my god.
I just love girls night. Like I really
do.
But I am rushing. Had to get ready
quick. I'm wearing my
silver heels and then
I'm doing these on the earrings.
Y'all know I love me a statement
earring. And these earrings are
literally [clears throat] perfect
for my outfit tonight.
It's going to complete the look
perfectly.
Like
perfect. And then I just did my lip
combo, so I'm going to add a little bit
of a lawless on top.
It's a nice pink finish. It's gorgeous.
So good. Mhm. So remember how we went to
Lush earlier today and I told y'all I
had that little
perfume thing? This is it.
And then I also have from Lush their
dusting powder and this is the
Supermilk. You guys know that's my
favorite scent from there.
And this I just put it on like
it's like a little roller. It's really
for travel, but I love this scent so
much. This is the American Cream scent.
I just push it up and put it behind my
ear.
On my palms where I'm going to put my
and just anywhere like throughout the
night and it's like a little freshen up
type of device and then to put it back
in you just press it.
Push it down.
And then for the dusting powder, you
just put it all on your arms. I just put
on my oil though, so actually I'm not
going to put this on right now.
But I just want to show you guys the
dusting powder that you put on. It
literally says this will probably fly
off the shelf so fast we don't even need
to write anything on the label. So it
doesn't even say you how to use it, you
just put it on your body and it smells
good all day. For tonight's scent I'm
using my Miu Miu.
And I spray so much everywhere. Now let
me go grab my bag and I'm going to show
y'all the final look. Bag of choice is a
chic tea. Okay, and then hopefully you
guys can see.
Here you guys have the full look. I
don't know.
I have my heels on but see,
but it's so cute and I'm ready to go and
I'm rushing. I am 20 minutes behind so
I'll see y'all when I see y'all.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
>> Short rib
bolognese.
No, it was the good combo. No, it was
what we were just talking about. It kind
of made me hot and bothered. I'm not
going to lie.
Girl, I mean we're having some really
steamy conversations tonight. You and
your homegirls y'all don't have
conversations like we do.
And that's the problem with y'all's
friendship. Y'all not real friends.
Y'all can't talk about stuff like this
that we talk about.
This Hugo is done.
He's talking about giving the camera no
how. This is my vlog.
>> [laughter]
>> Hey girl.
I'm home, you guys.
What a night, okay? I just had to come
on here.
My voice is already gone.
I just had to come on here, close out
the video.
Another [clears throat]
Another great successful girls night.
[laughter]
If you can't tell, you guys my baby was
so happy to see me.
Oh my god.
Hi buddy.
I'm going to take you go potty as soon
as I finish this, okay? I promise.
I promise. He's looking at me like,
"Take me out, please." But anyways, I
hope you guys enjoyed today's video. Did
we? We had a fun video today. We did. It
was a lot. We talked a lot. We did a
lot.
And I feel like you guys got to see my
business a little bit. But yeah, I hope
you guys enjoyed. I hope you loved. Do
not forget to let me know how your July
is going. And also, what you guys want
for the giveaway, too. Okay?
Okay? Also, too, if you're not following
me on Instagram,
we're not cool.
We're not cool, unless you don't have an
Instagram, cuz then that doesn't count.
But
you should be following me, right? Just
jokes, for real. But I love you guys,
and like always, I'll see you next week.
>> [music]
[music]